GANJEOLGOT CAPE HOPE MAILBOX
DESCEND CLUB'S THIRD QUEST IS REVEALED
YEONGNAM ALPS' 3-PEAK CHALLENGE
We're going to Ulsan.
-Hey!
-My home?
It's Tarzzan's home.
IT'S WHERE TARZZAN'S HOMETOWN
AND THE YEONGNAM ALPS ARE LOCATED
DESCEND CLUB WILL GO
ON AN EXPEDITION TO ULSAN
TEXTS FROM DOWOON
WHEN WE GO TO ULSAN, ARE WE GOING TO
MEET IN SEOUL AND GO TOGETHER?
WE'LL GATHER IN SEOUL
AND GO TOGETHER BY BUS
CAN I DRIVE DOWN IN MY OWN CAR?
WHY?
AFTER FILMING, I HAVE A FISHING SHOOT
DURING THE SEOLLAL HOLIDAY
OKAY
THE DAY THEY LEAVE FOR ULSAN
GANGNAM, SEOUL
A BLACK VEHICLE SLOWLY ENTERS
He's here.
Hello there!
Hello.
THE MINISTER OF TRANSPORT
GETS OUT SHYLY
Thank you so much for lending us
your car to travel during the holiday.
-Lend you my car?
-Yes.
-It's on the way for me anyway.
-Still.
MAKING SPACE IN HIS TRUNK
FOR THE OTHER MEMBERS' LUGGAGE
-Okay?
-Yeah.
-It'll be tight, but they'll go in.
-It'll work.
-Yeah.
-The rearview mirror is digital.
Right.
There's a fridge in here too.
Stop bragging about your car.
And it has a digital rearview mirror.
Should I lift the car a bit
so you can set the cameras up more easily?
I have to go to Wando afterwards.
-For fishing.
-For fishing?
I'm going to catch yellowtail for my fans.
AN EVENT FOR HIS FANS
HE'LL WAIT FOR THE OTHER MEMBERS
IN THE BASEMENT
A CUP OF COFFEE TO PREPARE
FOR THE LONG DRIVE AHEAD
Gosh.
His legacy.
Hi, Jung-won.
-I heard you're driving.
-Yes.
-You sure you won't be tired?
I mean, we're not even hiking there today.
-Hello.
I heard we're going in your car.
What's happening?
It'll be much more comfortable.
So you're really doing it?
IT SEEMS HE TOLD THEM
DURING THEIR SHOOT IN TAEBAEKSAN
By the way, Dowoon,
I saw what you did at your concert.
We saw it too.
"I'm close with Tarzzan." Was that it?
WHAT ARE THEY REFERRING TO?
And he said he touched his beard.
A FEW DAYS EARLIER
AT DAY6'S CONCERT IN DAEGU
I'm close with Tarzzan.
CHEERING
I got to hold Chae-min's hand.
EXCLAIMING
I even got to touch
Car, the garden's beard.
LAUGHING
The fans cheered when he talked about us.
But when he talked about Car-the's beard…
EMOTIONLESS LAUGHING
Right, I saw that too.
It's so embarrassing
that you saw me at my day job.
BLUSHING WITH EMBARRASSMENT
One of my relatives really likes hiking.
So I asked them
about what the trails are like.
They said Hallasan's easy
compared to them.
What?
Apparently, they're tougher.
In this quest?
-And they've been there?
-Yes.
What?
Weren't we told it wasn't tougher?
A SHOCKING NEWS THAT WAKES THEM UP
They hiked the same three peaks.
-They completed all three peaks?
-Yes.
When I said we'd hike the three peaks,
they said, "It won't be easy."
My car can go off-road.
AND SO, TARZZAN PLANNED
DESCEND CLUB'S EXPEDITION TO ULSAN
1. LUNCH AT HIS FAVORITE
MILMYEON RESTAURANT
Hey, Ulsan is really nice.
2. RIDE BICYCLES AT ULSAN GRAND PARK
Gosh, this is so nice!
3. CHECK IN AT BASE CAMP
4. HIKE THE YEONGNAM ALPS
5. VISIT PRESIDENT TAR'S FAMILY
A SPECIAL EVENT HAS ALSO BEEN PREPARED
DESCEND CLUB DEPARTS
FOR THEIR EXPEDITION TO ULSAN
-What a nice car.
-This is my first time.
Defenders are pretty nice.
THE MEMBERS LOVE DOWOON'S CAR
We'll be able to go comfortably
thanks to Dowoon.
LEAVING FOR ULSAN
Gosh, it's 371 km.
EXPECTED TO TAKE
ABOUT 4 HOURS AND 30 MINUTES
What are you doing during Seollal?
IT BEGINS THE DAY AFTER THE SHOOT
I'll be filling in for a radio DJ.
So you're working.
What about you, Tarzzan?
During the holiday?
I think I'll go to work at the studio.
-So this is when you'll visit your mother?
-That's right.
Let's each buy something for the family.
-Of course. I gladly will.
-It's Seollal after all.
That's what I'm most excited for.
Since I was a kid, I've loved
going to a friend's house to eat.
I asked my mom to do
only one thing for me.
It was to hide
my embarrassing photos from the past.
-It's fun to have those.
-Have you changed a lot?
I bet you haven't.
BABY TARZZAN
LOOKS THE SAME
I really want to see
how Chae-min looked as a kid.
-I bet you have some photos.
-I do.
This is how I looked as a kid.
-You look the same.
-He does.
BABY CHAE-MIN
BRIGHT-EYED
-You look a bit like Yi-jin.
-What?
Yi-jin's the kid who appeared
on my YouTube channel.
You kind of look like him.
I bet Dowoon was a super baby
when he was little.
-What's a "super baby"?
-What's that?
You know. Super babies.
They're babies
who just look absolutely adorable.
There are types of kids like Dowoon.
They're babies
who are always smiling in pictures.
And they're chuckling.
BABY DOWOON
CHUCKLING
I bet he was one of those babies
with big smiles in every photo.
I want to see your childhood photo.
-Me as a kid?
-Yes.
People loved me. I was so cute.
BABY CAR-THE?
CUTE…
Do kids still get milk
at school these days?
-You got chocolate milk if you paid more.
-Right.
-Did you guys do the milk delivery too?
-Milk duty? Yes.
THEY ALL HAVE SHARED EXPERIENCES
You didn't have kerosene heaters, right?
-We had them.
-I'm sure you did.
KEROSENE HEATERS WERE USED
WHEN CAR-THE AND DOWOON WERE STUDENTS
-You had those?
-Yeah.
Did you put your lunchboxes on it?
No lunchboxes.
TREATING HIM LIKE AN OLD-TIMER
We had kerosene duty though.
We had those things.
For chalkboard eraser dust…
The cleaner?
YOUNGER KIDS USED
ELECTRIC ERASER CLEANERS
We'd make it look like smoke
and go, "Fire!"
THEY PLAYED WITH THE ERASERS A LOT
THE ULTIMATE LITTLE BOY, TARZZAN
SEOUL
ULSAN
GOING SMOOTHLY IN DOWOON'S CAR
HE'S BEEN DRIVING
FOR 3 AND A HALF HOURS NOW
-Do you want to switch? Want me to drive?
-What?
There's about an hour left.
No, I'm good.
Feel free to tell me.
I say it if I'm tired.
-I just say it.
-All right.
DRIVING IS MORE SUITED
FOR THE MINISTER OF TRANSPORT THAN HIKING
I wonder why they picked
hiking of all things.
Do a lot of people go hiking these days?
Well, a lot of people I know around my age
go hiking, especially among guys.
The popularity of hiking
might've swayed them to make this show.
But once this show premieres,
what if the number of hikers decreases?
VIEWERS: "GOSH, I SHOULDN'T GO HIKING"
That's my ultimate goal.
Through this show,
I want to reduce the number of hikers.
This is what I'm worried about.
They might think,
"That looks so tough," and that's it.
What if it just ends with us suffering?
"I feel bad for them," and that's it?
Or they say,
"They're going through a lot."
IN THE MEANTIME, THE CAR KEEPS GOING
THEY ARRIVE IN DOWNTOWN ULSAN
Gosh.
I can feel it, Tarzzan.
I can feel that Ulsan is welcoming us.
Or is it turning us away with this wind?
Of course, it's welcoming us.
PRESIDENT TAR IS EXCITED TO BE BACK HOME
It must be nice to be back home, Tarzzan.
It's good to be home.
It is. And I'm at a loss for words.
It feels so…
That Ferris wheel is a landmark here.
And that's the department store.
This must be downtown.
IN HIS HOMETOWN,
HE NATURALLY BECOMES AN ULSAN DOCENT
That's my elementary school.
One of our producers
graduated from here too
GIGGLING YOUNG TARZZAN
Then, Jung-won,
how about we have the milmyeon noodles
and then go for a walk
in Ulsan Grand Park?
Sounds good.
DESCEND CLUB HEADS
TO THE MILMYEON RESTAURANT
This is the place. We're here.
-This is it?
-Look at the sign.
-It's the real deal.
-It's just like the others.
THEY CAN TELL BY THE FADED SIGN
THAT IT'S A GOOD RESTAURANT
Doesn't it already
smell like a good restaurant?
A FAVORITE RESTAURANT OF TARZZAN'S
FILLED WITH FOND MEMORIES
MILMYEON
Can we take over this place?
Let's take this place for ourselves.
This is amazing.
MANDU
THE FIRST MEAL IN ULSAN
IS MILMYEON AND MANDU
Can we go in?
It's this way.
Can we take over this place?
STARTS TALKING IN DIALECT UPON GETTING OUT
-Are you ready?
-Sir, can we take it over?
-We traveled 400 km for this.
-It's hot.
VERY EXCITED FOR FIRST MEAL
AFTER TRAVELING 400 KM
Hey, let me try a bowl of milmyeon.
Just one whole bowl.
Let's all get chilled broth ones.
-Four bowls of mul-milmyeon…
-And two dishes of mandu.
Two orders of mandu?
Hey, the owner even remembers
the last day you came.
Really?
Did you come here
with your mom on January 30?
-I come here every time I visit Ulsan.
-Really?
TARZZAN IS A TRUE REGULAR HERE
I've been coming here
since I was three or four years old.
This place serves
kid-size portions of noodles.
I used to eat the noodles
with a plastic fork as a kid.
The broth smells like
really good seolleongtang.
SNIFFING
You're right.
THEY TRY SOME WARM BROTH
BEFORE THE FOOD COMES OUT
Car-the, how do you feel about the broth?
First off, well…
TRYING TO TALK IN DIALECT AGAIN
It's hot.
And the spirit
of Gyeongsang people, you know.
It's full of that spirit.
The one without cucumbers is his.
We came from Seoul for this.
MILMYEON FILLED WITH GYEONGSANG SPIRIT
The broth is pretty clear.
-Let me check Ulsan's vibes with this.
-Okay.
This is the first impression.
Gosh, this is giving me pressure.
Everyone's liked it so far.
It sure is good.
Just from the broth, you know it's good.
So you've brought a lot of friends here?
Yeah.
Mandu.
-Excuse me.
-Thank you.
This place is good.
A NOSTALGIC TASTE
CHEWY NOODLES THAT ARE ADDICTIVE
AND A SPICY AND SWEET BROTH
This is the best.
FEELING VERY PROUD
This place is really good.
TODAY'S GUIDE FEELS REWARDED
EXCLAIMING IN SATISFACTION
It sure is good.
CAREFULLY TASTES THE MANDU AGAIN
I think they make their mandu fresh here.
The mandu is good.
He's a mandu expert.
I don't think they're store-bought.
FAVORITE FOOD
MANDU
Ma'am, you make the mandu yourself, right?
Yes, they're made by hand.
I knew it.
I'm fat for a reason.
I didn't gain weight for nothing.
LIKE A HUNGRY UNIT LEADER
POKING AROUND
-You can't eat that.
-Is that edible?
No.
-That's not a mandu wrapper.
-No.
I was checking the ripped cloth.
-I thought he was going to eat it.
-I thought you tried to eat it.
HE LOVES EATING FOOD, NOT CLOTH
Car, the garden's song,
"My Whole World."
I listen to it every day.
Hey, Car-the.
Ma'am, tell him.
What do you listen to every day?
"My Whole World."
YOU'VE BECOME MY WHOLE WORLD, MA'AM
YOU'VE LET ME TASTE MILMYEON
I'VE NEVER HAD BEFORE
She said so shyly,
"I listen to his song every day."
Ma'am, do you know DAY6 by any chance?
He's the drummer.
Hey, Ulsan is really nice.
Ma'am, I'm all done.
CELEBRATING HIS FINISHED BOWL
Gosh, what's that?
THEY'RE SURPRISED AT SOMETHING
-Did you put your trail snacks in there?
-Yeah.
How did you know?
If I put it in here,
I won't have to wear a backpack.
EASIER TO TAKE OUT AND EAT TOO
NEXT DESTINATION
MOVING TO ULSAN GRAND PARK
HEARING A CALL AS SOON AS THEY GET IN
Who are you suddenly calling?
It's just that…
I have a friend who lives here.
Tell him to come out.
Tell him to come to the park.
LET'S MEET DOWOON'S FRIEND
Hey, are you in Ulsan?
Yeah, I am.
Hey, I'm at Children's Grand Park…
No, I mean Ulsan Grand Park.
I'm at the park. Want to come?
I'm working the night shift today.
-When are you here until?
-The 13th.
Want to go hiking?
You're staying in Ulsan until the 13th?
Do you know the Young Alps in Ulsan?
YOUNG ALPS?
LAUGHING
What? Young…
I mean the Yeongnam Alps.
"Young Alps"!
THE "YOUNG ALPS" HIKER IS EMBARRASSED
Of course, I know.
Want to go hiking?
Call me again after you finish hiking.
Bye.
DISCUSSION IS OVER
"Young Alps"?
That was so…
MOCKING STARTS AS SOON AS HE HANGS UP
For a moment, I thought that
was what people called them here.
You can rent tandem bicycles at the park.
Nice. Let's take over the place.
THEY ARRIVE AT ULSAN GRAND PARK
It's been ages since I've been here.
LITTLE TARZZAN USED TO PLAY HERE
THE LARGEST URBAN PARK IN KOREA
Sir, we'd like to rent
two tandem bicycles.
DESCEND CLUB WILL BECOME CLOSER
WITH THE TANDEM BICYCLES
So how do we pair up?
Someone light should get on behind me.
-Should I ride with him?
-Sure.
WEIGHTS ARE BALANCED OUT
ON CAR-THE & TARZZAN'S BIKE
-Dowoon, I'll take the front.
-Okay.
FRONT AND REAR ARE SETTLED
ON CHAE-MIN & DOWOON'S BIKE
FOR TODAY, THEY'RE IN PAIRS
TO RIDE BICYCLES, NOT HIKE
I love this. The air is so nice.
The air is nice.
TAKING IN ALL THE FRESH AIR
RIDING TOGETHER
AND AS MUCH AS THEY PLEASE
They designed this park really well.
I know. It's really big.
It's like Central Park in Ulsan.
IT'S MUCH NICER AT THE PARK
SINCE THEY'RE TOGETHER
This is a really good date spot.
It's starting to feel like
a reality dating show.
How is it, Dowoon?
Oh, my gosh!
DO-SOON DOESN'T SEEM TO MIND
CHAE-CHEOL'S BICYCLE FLIRTING
WHEREAS JUNG-WON APPEARS
AS IF HE WANTS TO GO HOME
Later on at night…
Want to go hiking?
I don't think so.
PRETENDING NOT TO HEAR
That would get me rejected right away.
A BICYCLE DATE IN THE MOUNTAINS
BECOMES MORE AND MORE UNCERTAIN
I liked it. Thanks to Tarzzan…
He created fond memories for us.
IT MEANS HE LIKED THE BIKE RIDE
I don't really try to go to parks often.
But every time I go, it's nice.
So, it was nice when we went.
There's a famous slide here
that I used to play on as a kid.
Let's go there.
Sure, since we're here.
THEY GO LOOK FOR THE SLIDE
LITTLE TARZZAN PLAYED ON
Geez… It's uphill.
UPHILL ALL OF A SUDDEN
TANDEM BICYCLES AT ULSAN GRAND PARK
CAN BE RIDDEN UPHILL BUT NOT DOWNHILL
What is this?
QUICKLY GETS STEEPER
Hey, we need to think about this.
We're using up our energy!
-I think we made the wrong choice.
-Exactly.
-My legs are getting tired.
-We should've ridden that carriage!
We might not be able to hike tomorrow.
1ST LINEUP OF THE ULSAN GRAND PARK
MOUNTAIN BIKE RACE
Tarzzan, this isn't right.
Hey, stop. Let's turn back.
LEAD: CHAE-MIN & DOWOON
TAIL: CAR, THE GARDEN & TARZZAN
Hey, why…
Why are we doing this right now?
NEW SHOW IS CALLED
RIDE A MOUNTAIN BIKE!
Why are we doing this?
There's something called
"The Wishing Stone" on our right.
Don't explain, damn it!
What on earth?
They're mocking us, aren't they?
THEY DON'T HAVE THE ENERGY TO ANSWER
That over there
is why I brought you guys here.
-To come here?
-Yes.
-Okay.
-What is this place?
It's filled
with my childhood memories here.
A NOSTALGIC LONG SLIDE
It's so long.
THE SLIDE IS VERY LONG
AND THE BOTTOM LOOKS QUITE PAINFUL
Gosh, this slide is really long.
Wait.
We have to climb.
It's like Seoraksan.
What?
You packed your trail food earlier.
STOMACH PACKED WITH MILMYEON
Let's take a break up there.
DESCEND CLUB RULES
BREAKS: LESS THAN 5 MINUTES
A PREVIEW OF THE INSIDE OF THE SLIDE
2ND LINEUP OF THE ULSAN GRAND PARK HIKE
LEAD: CAR, THE GARDEN
THEY FIND IT HILARIOUS
TO SEE HIM SLIDE DOWN
CAR, THE GARDEN
SCREAMING
It's really loud.
A SILENT SCREAM
My butt hurts so fucking much!
My butt!
PAIN ON THE BACKSIDE AS EXPECTED
AFTER ENJOYING THE NOSTALGIC PLAYGROUND
Hey, Dowoon.
Thank you for coming, everyone.
THEY LEAVE FOR BASE CAMP
I feel a bit bad.
Why would you? It was fun. Seriously.
-Don't be sorry.
-Right.
"Alps Guesthouse."
Is that the name?
BASE CAMP IS NEAR THE YEONGNAM ALPS
"Baenae Golyeongnam Alps Guesthouse."
Still, I bet it'll be nice.
They always pick the best accommodations.
This is it. "Yeongnam Alps."
BAENAEGOL YEONGNAM ALPS
TODAY'S ACCOMMODATIONS
ARE SURROUNDED BY THE YEONGNAM ALPS
YEONGNAM ALPS
THE PERFECT BASE CAMP FOR THE DESCEND CLUB
THE MEMBERS ARE ASSIGNED
TO THE BIGGEST ONE
-Thank you, Dowoon.
-Thank you so much.
My pleasure.
GRUNTS
TAKING THEIR LUGGAGE IN
Geez, there are stairs everywhere.
CAR, THE GARDEN ENTERS FIRST
QUICKLY LOOKING AROUND
It really feels like a guesthouse here.
IT IS A GUESTHOUSE
This place is like… You know?
Where Cho Seung-woo, Ji Jin-hee stayed…
-With Hwang Jung-min.
-Yeah.
The vibe here reminds you of them.
A SOFA THAT CATCHES YOUR EYE
THE MINISTER OF TRANSPORT
IS AWAY IN DREAMLAND
I should take a nap too.
Why is he twitching his shoulder?
He's asleep.
Is that a sleep habit?
He keeps doing it.
Maybe he's playing the drums?
HE CAN'T HELP BUT RECORD IT
TARZZAN'S PHONE CAMERA
TYPICAL SLEEP HABIT OF DRUMMERS
SNORING
WITHIN 3 MINUTES,
THEY HEAR FAMILIAR SNORING
OFF AGAIN TO CHECK
TARZZAN'S PHONE CAMERA
SNORE, THE GARDEN
AND SO, DESCEND CLUB HAS A PEACEFUL TIME
IN THE MEANTIME
THEY HAD A SMALL WISH
I want to film Earth Arcade.
I'm so envious of them.
I'm so jealous.
Are we playing
Guess the Celebrities today?
I think I'd be so good at it.
OBSESSED WITH EARTH ARCADE
Let's decide by playing
Guess the Celebrities.
I want to play
Guess the Celebrities so bad.
SINCE HE WANTED TO PLAY IT SO MUCH
THE PRODUCTION CREW
IS PREPARING A SIMPLE ACTIVITY
On your way out,
please take your backpacks with you.
-Okay.
-Just your backpacks.
You mean our hiking backpacks?
Yes.
WITHOUT KNOWING WHY,
THEY EACH TAKE THEIR BACKPACKS
AND MOVE TO THE ACTIVITY AREA
You can finally play
the Guess the Celebrities game you wanted.
I'm really good at it.
Even if you know,
you get flustered
when they're suddenly shown.
You think so?
A FAMILIAR SCENE ON TV
You end up like that.
You're right.
There it is.
Gosh, it's scary.
They made it look so serious.
-It looks serious.
-It's kind of set up like Earth Arcade.
ACTIVITY AREA
There are a lot of cameras.
THE SET LAYOUT THEY'VE SEEN A LOT ON TV
We're finally doing Earth Arcade.
Come on in.
Hey, it's Earth Arcade!
Come in and have a seat first.
It's time for activities.
-Dowoon. Are you okay?
-Yes? Yes.
HE'S STILL HALF ASLEEP
THE FIERY RED PRESIDENT ALSO ENTERS
THEY'VE ALL ENTERED WITH THEIR BACKPACKS
HE PREPARED THE FINGER STICK TOO
Gosh, he has that stick too.
THEY'VE ONLY SEEN IT BEFORE ON TV
It finally feels like a variety show.
You guys are in trouble today.
This is so cool.
You'll end up saying,
"Please make me go hiking."
This is amazing.
THE EARTH ARCADE FAN FINDS EVERYTHING COOL
We're going to do a group mission.
All four of you will team up.
We'll play a simple game
to determine whether you succeed or fail.
This is already so nice. Why go hiking?
If I were watching this,
I'd think, "This will be fun!"
If I were a viewer,
I'd already be excited.
I think hiking is more fun,
but you guys wanted to do this so badly.
-Let us try.
-We'll give you a taste.
-We should at least have a taste.
-Just a taste.
It's like free samples at a supermarket.
It's just a tasting.
How about we bet something small?
Nothing related to hiking, right?
What do you think it'll be?
If we win, would the number of peaks
shrink from three to two?
But what if you fail
and have to hike four peaks?
Should I stop talking?
Now, why do you think
we asked you to bring your backpacks?
Wait, are we putting things in them?
More stuff!
It's more stuff!
Wait, that's a good idea too.
THAT WASN'T IT
We didn't think of that.
Why backpacks? I have no idea.
Chae-min, show us yours.
You have kilometer badges
that you've worked so hard to earn.
If we play with nothing at stake,
it would be no fun.
You guys are about to reach
50 km soon.
CURRENT TOTAL DISTANCES
If you reach 50 km,
-we'll give you gold badges.
-Okay.
PRIZE FOR 50 KM: A GOLD BADGE
If you reach 100 km,
we'll give you the right to change
the theme of our show as you like.
IF THEY REACH 100 KM,
THEY CAN CHANGE THE SHOW
You guys are about to reach
50 km soon.
So at this critical juncture,
we'll play a game,
and you'll bet a kilometer per round.
I wondered why
they were suddenly doing this.
They saw us
and were starting to get nervous.
They thought they were being too generous.
SCARED
No, this is really good for you.
For every round, 1 km is on the line.
We can win them too?
-Yes, we'll give them to you.
-We'll just win then.
FAIL AND LOSE 1 KM
WIN AND EARN 1 KM
That's if you win.
Then, the show might change right away.
INTRIGUED
Do you hate hiking that much?
We just need to win 50 rounds.
FEELS SO FAR AWAY
HIKING SEEMS EASIER
Just 50 rounds!
If anyone gets something wrong,
let's not blame them too much.
Let's not doubt each other.
Be encouraging.
We're one team, right?
HESITATING
I thought, "He and I are a team?"
"But he's so handsome."
I mean, his eyes looked so…
Because I've never had anyone
who was this handsome
on the same team as me.
I was like, "Thanks, man."
NO GUESS THE CELEBRITIES
DUE TO PUBLICITY RIGHTS ISSUES
We have something else.
Let's start with a simple one.
"The Category Game."
-Okay, "The Category Game."
-I'll explain what it is.
-There are many kinds of ramyeon.
-Right.
Say a name of ramyeon.
Chae-min first. Go.
Samyang Ramen.
-Snack Ramen.
-Next. Okay.
-Next.
-Shin Ramyun.
-Nongshim Ramyun.
Next. What?
-It's not Nongshim Ramyun?
-Wrong.
-Yeul Ramen.
-But there is Nongshim Ramyeon.
-Really?
-Come on.
-It was released.
-Hey!
-I was right then!
-See?
Viewers would be like,
"That ramyeon exists though!"
"This is so fun!"
Look at how fun this is.
I feel like I'm losing all my confidence
because of this show.
It's fine, but do we get a practice round?
Should we do that?
-Let's do a practice one.
-Yes.
Okay, let's do it.
PRACTICE ROUND
Chae-min will start.
Gosh, I feel nervous.
What's your favorite hobby, Dowoon?
-Fishing.
-Fishing, right?
So when you go fishing, you catch fish.
Okay, out of fish names,
say a name that ends with "chi" in Korean.
Chae-min first. One, two, three.
-Jagalchi.
-Nalchi.
-"Jagalchi"?
-Yes.
Let's check later.
-Next.
-Nalchi.
-Chamchi or tuna.
Chamchi.
-Next.
-Myeolchi or anchovy.
Next.
Darangi geonban chamchi.
"Darangi geonban chamchi"?
ON EGGSHELLS
-What else was there? Think.
-Galchi.
I was stuck too.
"Stuck-chi!"
What were you thinking of?
Nothing. I was done.
-Your mind went blank?
-Yes.
-Okay, "chi."
-That was hard.
Let's go.
-Fish names are difficult.
-Yeah.
But how do we win?
How many laps do we need to do?
IF THEY MAKE ONE FULL LAP, THEY WIN
-I think we'll lose them all.
-That can't happen.
They must be doing this to take them all.
-And they'll take us to higher mountains.
-With ridiculous quizzes.
They didn't do this last week.
THEY SEE THE PLANS CLEARLY
-They must be anxious.
-Yeah. Right?
FYI GOLD PRICES
WERE SKYROCKETING ON DATE OF FILMING
We can give you gold if we have to.
-So a kilometer is on the line.
-Okay.
Here goes the first round.
FAIL: LOSE 1 KM
WIN: EARN 1 KM
We can do it.
I'm nervous.
I'm so nervous.
We'll start with Chae-min,
go to Dowoon, and end back at Chae-min.
Now, we're in Tarzzan's hometown.
What is it called?
-Ulsan.
-Yes, we're in Ulsan.
Say a word that starts
with "ul" in Korean.
-Chae-min first. One, two, three!
-Ulbo.
-One, two, three!
-Uljin.
-Ulju County.
-One, two, three!
-Ulleong or nauseous.
One, two, three!
-Ulbin.
-Wrong!
What on earth is that?
-What's "ulbin"?
-"Ulbin"?
-Ulbin.
-Wrong!
What on earth is that?
What's "ulbin"?
-What's "ulbin"?
-"Ulbin"?
You can look it up.
-You have to explain.
-First off…
You can do it. What's "ulbin"?
-What's "ulbin"?
-What is it?
"Eating bindae-tteok while crying."
FRUSTRATED TO TEARS
-That's…
-Can you check if it exists?
-There was Ulleungdo Island.
-Right.
RIGHT…
But this spot is tough.
What were you going to say, Car-the?
-Ulleungdo Island.
-Not bad.
I was going to say Ulleungdo Island.
I just told him.
THE SLY BEARDED ONE
Your mind goes blank
because you get nervous.
There was a lot, like "ulkeok."
But I couldn't think of it in the moment.
Ulgeum or turmeric.
Uldae or Adam's apple.
Right.
A lot of them come to mind
after the game ends.
So that was a practice round, right?
Yeah, a practice round.
All right, thank you.
-What?
-Okay, a kilometer each.
TAKES A 1-KM BADGE FROM EVERYONE
Tarzzan, give him one more.
What?
Just like that,
we already lost a kilometer each.
We lost a total of 4 km already.
You lost about 30 minutes
of hiking from Seongpanak trail.
Now that you explain it that way…
A SHOCKING NEWS
It's a game where time is stolen.
ABOUT TO CRY
We just lost
a whole section of stairs in time.
Right…
Now that I think of it that way,
it's so sad.
Right?
Okay, what now then?
Should we stop?
-Yes, let's stop.
-Let's stop.
VERY WISE
In my opinion…
Let's stop here.
-I mean, we got a little taste.
-You did.
We're done now.
But shouldn't you play one more round
to recover your losses?
This is how gambling works.
-Should we raise the stakes?
-"You should get it back."
THE CRYING BINDAE-TTEOK EATER
IS AGGRESSIVE
A guy like you will end up losing an arm.
You're hopeless.
-"Raise the stakes"!
-I mean…
I can't stand to see them take our stuff.
We have to win.
Then, shall we raise it to 2 km?
-No, just 1 km.
-No, let's do it like this instead.
You all bet 1 km,
and if you fail, we'll take 1 km.
But we get 2 km if we win?
If you succeed, we'll give you 2 km each.
-We should take this deal.
-Of course.
AN INCREDIBLE OFFER
-We'll take that deal.
-Gosh, that's…
MAKE IT DOUBLE
You can double the winnings. Is that okay?
Then, let's play one more round and stop.
-They're offering 2 km.
-Okay, let's do it.
-Shall we play?
-Yes, let's do it.
Chae-min will go first.
Chae-min first.
Is the same direction okay?
Or you can start with Dowoon,
then go to Chae-min,
and end back at Dowoon.
I need time to think though.
Or should we change it? Should I go first?
You go first.
Yes, let's try that.
You were like,
"Let's see how you do. You go first."
A LACK OF TRUST
You go first.
-Dowoon first?
-Okay.
Okay, Dowoon will go first.
The oldest among you is Car, the garden.
His stage name is Car, the garden.
Like his name,
say the name of a singer or group
with four syllables.
Hold on a second.
Dowoon first. One, two, three.
To More Raw.
One, two, three.
I'll give you plenty of time.
I'm sorry,
but what's the group Dowoon is in?
DAY6
What group is your friend in?
-It's DAY6!
-DAY6.
EVEN THE DAY6 MEMBER DIDN'T KNOW
How can we play any game with you guys?
How do you expect to play games like this?
Hey, he's hopeless.
-But…
-Absolutely hopeless.
Trust me, he's…
What did you come up with?
I was thinking DAY6 and XIA Junsu.
And I kept thinking of TVXQ.
U-Know Yunho and XIA Junsu.
THE FOUR-SYLLABLE NICKNAME HOLDER EXCELS
-Mine was Cherry Filter.
-Cherry Filter?
Hey, we have no chance.
Dowoon, he can't do this.
We'll be crushed.
To More Raw really does exist.
-Did you guess?
-Yes.
It really exists.
BRIGHT, INNOCENT SMILE
He even guessed too.
Girls' Generation.
-Girls' Generation.
-No Brain.
TWICE is from your agency.
Doesn't your agency have another one?
I'm not close with them.
What does that have to do with this?
Good point.
Good point. You're right.
Are you close with To More Raw?
Did you mention them
because you know them?
THE WEAK LINKS ARE REVEALED
AFTER JUST TWO ROUNDS
This was such an easy one. What a shame.
Could you let this one slide, please?
Just this once.
Let's give them a pass.
Can't we have Chae-min go first?
-I need time to think.
-Okay, Chae-min's first again.
We need time to think.
-We're slow.
-But we have to come up with two.
Then, let's have Tarzzan sit there.
I'll sit over there.
I think Tarzzan
is a bit short on information.
You're right.
TARZZAN GOES TO THE EASY SPOT
This is your last chance.
If you fail this time, we'll take 1 km.
-But if you succeed, you get 2 km.
-We get 2 km.
RETRY
Chae-min will go first.
Say a word that ends with "kkang."
Chae-min will go first. One, two, three.
-Saeukkang or Shrimp Crackers.
-Next.
-Roasted Pollack Crackers.
Damn it!
Wrong!
What a relief! I had no idea!
Damn it!
They said all the answers already.
HE ALSO DIDN'T HAVE ANY IDEAS
UNPRECEDENTEDLY THE WEAKEST LINK
Geez, you guys are hopeless.
We should teach you
a proper lesson this time.
What? Isn't it over now?
You asked to play games
when you're this bad?
Hey, isn't this a difficult spot?
But the thing is…
I apologize. We'll do what you say.
Because these two…
I did have a bad feeling about them.
But they're not really interested
in what's going on in society.
They just go about their own lives.
And I can clearly see that now.
I'm sorry,
but Car-the, please collect
the 1 km badges and give them to us.
These two sure are smart.
Actually, it has nothing to do
with being smart.
Chae-min, give these two a quiz.
Words that begin with something.
GLARING
Chae-min's eyes looked so scary just now.
HE'S VERY COMPETITIVE
The thing is, I wanted to play games,
but Chae-min really wanted to play.
But since it turned out like this,
he's feeling pretty disappointed.
He didn't expect this.
DEVASTATED EARTH ARCADE FAN
Okay, four-character idioms.
BLINKING
"Four-character idioms"!
One lap… You can just do two laps.
Okay, start!
"The student is now the master."
"Utter chaos."
-"Put oneself in others' shoes."
-He's good.
"Four-character idiom."
WINNER
You should've just said
"North, South, East, West."
Or "A, B, C, D."
We really don't do this.
But we'll make it 3 km.
Hey, this is…
You can just bet 1 km each.
Won't this just lead to more disaster?
-We're being suckered.
-Or…
Or we can do this. If you bet 2 km,
you could win 6 km.
A MORE SENSATIONAL OFFER
It's high return, but high risk.
But with such risk factors that we have…
RISK FACTOR 1, RISK FACTOR 2
If we succeed just once, we break even.
One for three is better.
One for three?
If you win 3 km, you almost break even.
We can recover our losses
and end the game.
-Let's do this one and then decide.
-Okay.
But even if we lose again,
we can just bet double again, right?
GAMBLING ADDICTION WARNING
Hey! But you know what?
If we keep going as he just said,
and if we lose everything,
we should use it
as a public awareness campaign.
Instead of showing people
trembling with greed,
just show him saying,
"Hey, we can just win it all back!"
Then, show him
losing everything and going hiking.
A HIKING END
WHY DO WE GAMBLE?
They had it all planned out.
Use it as a public service announcement.
I just want to recover our losses.
SINCE THEY'RE MUCH WORSE THAN EXPECTED…
Maybe we should do "Finish the Phrase."
For example,
-North, South…
-East, West.
-Yes, that's it.
-Right, this game.
CHANGING THE GAME
This game's a bit of a…
-A solo competition.
-I think we'll fail right away.
Our show, Take a Hike!,
will be streamed where?
-Netflix.
-Yes, Netflix.
This game will be about movie, drama,
and variety show titles on Netflix.
I like that.
Chae-min will go first.
HIS FACE CONTORTS IN AGONY
HIS FACE CONTORTS TOO
Hold on. Hey!
They can't do this!
WILL THEY DO BETTER?
But Dowoon is also…
Chae-min will go first. Here we go.
-Single's…
-Inferno!
All of Us…
-Are Dead.
-Correct.
Stranger…
Who's that?
No! I'll answer it instead!
Stranger…
-Who's that?
-No!
HE TURNS INTO A TYRANT
Who's that?
No! I'll answer it instead!
CHAOS
Can I answer it instead? Just this once.
Can you believe this?
"Stranger Who's That?"
I'll answer the "Stranger" one.
-Stranger…
-Things.
Wait, I heard it as the name "Kim Ui-han."
-So… Hold on. Seriously.
-Right!
Wait, I heard it as the name "Kim Ui-han."
FEELING WRONGED
-Seriously.
-That's why he was flustered!
That's why he asked, "Who's that?"
Seriously, I'm not exaggerating.
That's why I asked, "Who's that?"
BURSTING INTO LAUGHTER
Of course, he'd get flustered.
The finger!
The finger fell off!
Come on, that's ridiculous!
Of course, if I heard "Stranger,"
I would've said "Things."
No way!
Who's Kim Ui-han?
-You can check the footage.
-No way!
I mean, you heard me ask, "Who's that?"
-Yes, he asked, "Who's that?"
-Yeah.
If I heard "Stranger,"
I wouldn't say, "Who's that?"
-Are Dead.
-Correct.
Stranger…
Who's that?
No! I'll answer it instead!
ISN'T FEELING WRONGED AT ALL
If he thought he heard a name,
he obviously would be confused.
-Yeah.
-He suddenly heard a name.
If it were me,
I would've reacted the same way.
If I heard "Stranger,"
I would've said "Things" for sure.
Seriously?
I even downloaded
some episodes of Stranger Things.
If you really did, I'll let it slide.
Okay, dude.
Yeah, that's right. Show him!
CONFIDENT
If you really did, I'll let it slide.
Yeah. He has the episodes!
He really has them!
He has them.
-He really downloaded them.
-Yeah!
Producer Nah's pronunciation
was the issue.
Yeah, like who on earth is Kim Ui-han?
Who is that?
WE WILL ROOT
FOR ALL THE KIM UI-HAN'S IN THE WORLD
Okay, let's do it again.
AS PROMISED, IT DIDN'T COUNT
But "All of Us" was a bit confusing.
Yeah, I almost said…
-"Be with You."
I almost said that.
But there's that too.
The Korean movie version.
We'll give you a warning.
-It was close.
-Yes, it was close.
CHANGING SEATS AGAIN
I think I watched
All of Us Are Dead recently.
I wish I got Stranger Things.
I mean, I know that show too.
But I heard it as "Kim Ui-han."
"Kim Ui-han"!
STILL SO FUNNY
Imagine how flustered he must've been.
He suddenly got a name.
We won't count the Stranger Things one.
-The wager is the same, right?
-Yes.
-One for three kilometers.
-Okay.
One for three.
The category is still about Netflix.
RETRY
The category is titles.
Chae-min will go first.
KPop…
-Demon Hunters.
-Correct.
The Devil's…
-Plan.
-Correct.
Night…
-Of Arcade.
-Wrong!
COLLAPSES
"Night of Arcade"!
LAUGHING
KOREAN TITLE SOUNDED LIKE
NAKWON MUSICAL INSTRUMENT ARCADE
Hey, have you ever been to Nakwon Arcade?
Don't you go there to buy instruments?
BARELY ABLE TO RECOVER
Have you ever been there?
OR MAYBE NOT
HAPPY MR. KIM UI-HAN
How am I supposed to play
any game with you guys?
Was it Night in Paradise? Is that right?
I mean, I knew the first two!
Why do I always get ones I don't know?
That was funny, but--
It's so unfair.
I mean, have you ever been
to Nakwon Arcade?
Car-the, I knew the first two--
I mean, you're a hip-hop artist.
Why would you say Nakwon Arcade?
It'd be understandable
if it were me who said it. Geez.
What was the answer?
-Night in Paradise.
Starring Um Tae-goo.
But my Netflix account is in English,
so the titles are different.
It's in English?
For example, Stranger Things
is shown in its English title.
Stranger what?
LISTEN AND REPEAT
What about Solo Jiok?
Then, Tarzzan's at a disadvantage.
Then, you wouldn't know Night in Paradise.
For me, when someone says "Nakwon,"
I think "Arcade."
"Nakwon Arcade."
That was hilarious.
We might lose all our kilometers.
THEY ALL LOSE 3 KM
Or…
I think you should bet 2 km
to win 6 km and fix things all at once.
-And it'll be--
-No, we're good.
MINISTER OF FOREIGN AFFAIRS IS FIRM
You should discuss it.
Let's go with one for three.
Dowoon will go first.
-It's titles on Netflix.
-Okay.
When Life…
-Gives You Tangerines.
-Correct.
Culinary…
-Class Wars.
-Correct.
-Physical…
-100.
Correct.
You and…
-Everything Else.
-Correct!
Money…
-Heist.
-Correct!
IF THESE TWO GET IT RIGHT, THEY SUCCEED
Three Idiots…
-Wrong!
-Jinny's…
-Hey! You!
-No, wait!
-What's with you?
-Wait!
He made the show!
Right, exactly! Three Idiots
with Lee Seo-jin…
What are you talking about? Wrong!
With Lee Seo-jin…
IDIOTS IN KENYA…
What are you talking about? Wrong!
You little…
ANSWER: THREE IDIOTS IN KENYA
"Three Idiots with Lee Seo-jin
and Kim Gwang-gyu?"
Tarzzan, that's another spinoff show.
THREE IDIOTS IN KENYA
READY OR NOT: TEXAS
I know it
but couldn't recall the title…
SO CLOSE TO SUCCEEDING
By the way, what was the next one?
Give us the next one.
If you get this one right…
-You must answer right away.
-Okay.
Better Late…
-Is Okay.
-Wrong!
Better Late…
-Is Okay.
-Wrong!
BETTER LATE THAN SINGLE'S PANELIST
IS DUMBFOUNDED
"Better Late Than I'm Solo"?
Wait, that's not it.
Better Late…
It's not "Is Okay"?
Dowoon's saying,
"I understand how you feel."
I'm sure this comforted people.
He's saying that it's okay.
LEGS GIVE OUT
-He said, "It's okay"?
-It's not "Is Okay"?
It's not "Okay"!
He was telling us,
like the lecturer Kim Chang-ok.
So, the title's "It's Not Okay."
-What are you talking about?
-No!
WORN OUT
-So what is it?
-What is it?
Isn't it "Than Single"?
Oh, "Than Single."
Come on, that's your oldest member's show.
DEEP SIGH
-It's okay though.
-But Dowoon…
You should watch Season 2.
I'm sorry, but you two make my head hurt.
JUST LIKE THE GWANEUMSA TRAIL
I'll be honest.
I was looking here
and then turned this way.
And it gave me stress.
MORE STRESS-INDUCING THAN HIKING
If we pick a topic we're interested in,
we can do well.
What are you confident in?
-Could you listen to them?
-Clothing brands.
If it's about clothing brands,
I can outlast everyone.
Clothing brands? I only know Nike.
Same here.
See? We just have different interests.
Dowoon, what are you confident in?
If it's about fish, he'd be the best.
I'm never playing this game again.
THEY ALL LOSE 4 KM
How did we lose everything so fast?
LOST HALF OF TAEBAEKSAN HIKING
This show is scary.
THEY CHANGE THE GAME
Abbreviations.
It's the Abbreviations Quiz.
For example, "TAE" means
"they abbreviate everything."
-Like this.
-That's right.
"IHGH."
-Let's do it.
-"I hate going hiking."
I just made it up.
-IHGH. "I hate going hiking."
-I just made it up.
Let's make it 5 km.
We'll give you 5 km.
Bet 1 km and win 5 km?
-You can break even.
-Should we do it?
-Let's do it.
-It's doable.
For this game,
I got a good feeling just now!
GAMBLING ADDICTION WARNING
-Hey! Let's get back our kilometers.
-Let's push on.
Let's go!
TARZZAN'S SHOUT
This will practically be
the last round, right?
Here we go. Chae-min will go first.
"BM."
-"Baedal Minjok."
-Correct.
"DCC."
-"Dubai chewy cookie."
-Correct.
"Yoajung."
"Yogurt ice cream is really delicious."
Wrong!
REALLY WRONG
Even when he started to say "yogurt,"
it was already so frustrating.
What on earth were you talking about?
He sounded like a foreigner.
"Yogurt ice cream is really delicious."
Just think about it.
Why would the name be
"Yogurt ice cream is really delicious"?
Why would they?
They could just keep that to themselves.
Why abbreviate what they're exclaiming?
Why do you always give me difficult ones?
I knew Baedal Minjok.
So what does Yoajung mean?
Okay, what does Yoajung mean?
"Yogurt ice cream…"
What's the last part?
Isn't it "Done Right"?
But in the midst of it all,
"He let his pronunciation slide."
That's what I thought.
-You're right.
-You didn't say anything.
I was so grateful.
"Really delicious" made me really angry.
To be honest,
"Three Idiots with Lee Seo-jin"
really made me mad too.
TARZZAN'S BEST PHRASES
NIGHT OF ARCADE
AND THREE IDIOTS WITH LEE SEO-JIN
-What was the next question?
-What was it?
Give us the loser's second chance.
"The loser's second chance."
HE JUST MADE UP YET ANOTHER PHRASE
-He's broken.
-"The loser's second chance."
Isn't it "a second chance game"?
ZZAN OF TAR
KIM UI-HAN
-All right, then.
-Yes?
Okay, the two of you will take turns.
-Okay.
-Two questions each.
THE TWO GENIUSES GO FOR A DO-OVER
If you succeed,
we won't count the last one.
By the way, thank you so much.
We mean it.
You're so generous.
Then, what does that make me?
-No, he really is generous.
-Yeah.
And going to all these lengths shows
they really think of us
as idiots at this point.
FEELING BITTER
Here we go.
WITH A DO-OVER ON THE LINE
-We'll make it easy.
-Okay.
These are so easy.
"LMO."
-"Looks make the outfit."
-Correct.
"OAL."
"Obviously sturdy…"
What was that?
-"OA…"
-What?
"Obviously sturdy
and lasting human wall."
APPLAUDING
Hey, that's correct!
DUMBFOUNDED
So you knew!
How did you know?
-Really?
-Wrong!
"Obviously high
and lasting wall of humans"?
"Obviously sturdy
and lasting human wall."
-Go through the words again.
-"Human wall."
"Gosh, Car-the is OAL."
Yeah, OAL.
I guess we gave him one that was too hard.
Yes, OAL is too difficult.
But for others, OAL isn't that…
-Not hard at all, right?
-It's not hard.
Wait, so what's OAL?
-What does it mean?
-"Another level."
It stands for "another level"?
Yeah.
OAL means "another level"?
LMO means "looks make the outfit."
But OAL means…
"On."
Oh, "on a level"?
"Another level."
So, OAL stands for "on another…"
Who are you fighting with?
It looks like he's fighting
with his own self.
He's trying to make himself understand.
He's arguing with himself.
Wait, look.
-DCC is "Dubai chewy cookie."
-Yes.
OAL is "another level"?
It starts with… "on."
-"Another level."
-"On."
He really is something.
HE FINALLY UNDERSTANDS IT
"On another level."
People like you are "on another level."
"On another level." I see.
Man, if you had never learned
how to play the drums…
-You'd be struggling too.
-Okay, I got it now.
BORN TO BE A DRUMMER
If you each get two questions right,
we'll let things slide.
-It's for them.
-Good luck.
"IAEIF."
"Iced Americano even if freezing."
-Okay!
-That was great.
It's looking good.
"SELP."
Three, two…
"Scrounge everything and pull…" Damn.
It's right, isn't it? It was similar.
"Scrape every last penny"!
Yes, that's right! Correct!
-"Every last penny"!
-Yes, that's right!
Correct!
They counted it as correct!
You don't have to put a time limit.
DODGED A BULLET
"SNC."
"Seeking a natural connection"!
Yes!
Here comes the last one.
NIS.
What?
You know this. Think carefully.
National Intelligence Service!
-Yes!
-Chae-min.
-Yes?
People all around Asia
will be watching this.
-I don't know anything about that.
-Many children will be watching.
It's important to show
we're honest and trustworthy.
While walking by him just now,
did you, by any chance,
though I doubt it,
tell him the answer?
If you say no, we'll have to believe you.
Chae-min's not like that.
Did you tell him or not?
Did I tell you or not?
Did he tell me or not?
-Yes or no?
-I didn't hear anything.
He said he didn't hear anything.
I just thought,
"Gosh, I knew Dowoon could do it."
I mean, he could've just said your name.
-Your name is Jung-won.
-Yeah, it sounds similar.
-Car, the Jung-won.
-Yeah.
-Car, the Jung-won!
National Intelligence Service!
You knew the answer, right?
Of course, he did.
How could he not know it?
Every Korean should know this.
See? He says he knew.
You knew about the NIS, right?
Of course.
-You knew?
-Of course.
I'll have our sound mixer check the facts.
But if our sound mixer
checks the sound levels later
and notices Chae-min's lips and voice
saying "National Intelligence Service,"
then to all the young fans around Asia
who expected honesty…
Then, you'd truly be a tyrant.
-You have to just push ahead.
-Simply a tyrant.
"He's a real tyrant like his character."
"Oh, that tyrant?"
I told him the answer.
HE COMES CLEAN
-Chae-min is…
-Bring us the 5 km badges.
Give us the 5 km badges.
Chae-min chose honesty in the end.
In various interviews,
I said my strength is honesty, so…
I couldn't bring myself to keep lying.
You may get another chance
to win these kilometers back.
I'm sure you'll get the chance.
It might get hard on you
if we keep going, so shall we wrap up?
THEY END LOSING 5 KM EACH
But regardless of the result
of these games,
I can't think of any way to win them back.
Exactly.
Getting angry and stealing them
or taking them by force are the only ways.
THE NEXT DAY
Let's go.
Come over here.
WHILE HIKING THE YEONGNAM ALPS
We should head out.
-Let's move out.
-Let's go.
By the way, where's Producer Nah?
I think he's way behind us.
No, I think he took a car down
from that rest stop earlier.
At some point,
we didn't see him climbing up.
I realized he abandoned us.
PRODUCER NAH HAS DISAPPEARED
-Jung-won.
-Yeah?
You know Yung-suk ran off, right?
Yeah. When did he leave?
I mean, after he took
our badges like that yesterday…
I feel so angry all of a sudden.
I've never seen him
say anything like that before.
What did I do wrong? What is it?
Chae-min, why are you so angry?
PRODUCER NAH IS BACKED INTO A CORNER
Where were you earlier?
EVERY TIME SOMEONE STEPS AWAY
SECRET DEALS ARE MADE
-I only drink Sprite.
-Chae-min only drinks Sprite.
There are two cups. How strange.
NEW SUSPICIOUSLY CLOSE TIES
Congratulations on climbing
the three peaks.
COLLUSION DISGUISED AS RECONCILIATION
What a shame.
Still, let's give him a hand.
Why?
AND THE ONE LEFT OUT
You jerks made a deal while I was away!
I hurried my way down
and gave all of you rides!
-You little…
-Dowoon.
I thought highly of you!
Hear me out.
Subtitle translation by: Wayne Ryu